Master?
You?
Don’t make me laugh, psycho!
I’m the one holding my wedding here.
I chose this cathedral.
Who else would it be?
Hahaha!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Everyone knows Lord Redmond is the only heir.
You're just a dumped, broke loser!
Stop wasting breath on this trash.
Throw him in the dungeons.
Jack, they’re attacking Severin!
I'll take these tin cans down with me!
We may be lowborn,
but we won’t just stand here and take this!
You filthy lowborns!
You dare to challenge me?
You stole his title,
you stole his wife,
and now you want to butcher him in a church?!
There is no freaking justice in Golantis!
Justice?
For slaves?
If you're so eager to die for this loser,
I'll send you all to hell together!
I’ll call the Black Market Blades right now to butcher you all!
Blade Master!
Get to the Holy Cathedral and butcher them all!
You’re all dead.
The Blade Master are coming.